A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Central Files, Series 3 FA378
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File, 2
  - Real Property (RA), 46
    - RA 1 - Acquisition-Requirements (Box 187)
    - RA 2 - Buildings - Plant Management (Box 187)
    - RA 2-1 - Guest Houses - Blair House - White (Box 187)
    - RA 3 - Concessions (GSI) (Box 187)
    - RA 4 - Construction - Design (Box 187)
    - RA 5 - Disposal - Surplus - Real Estate (Box 187)
  - Recreation - Sports (RE), 47
    - RE - RECREATION - SPORTS (Box 187)
    - RE 1 - Basketball (Box 187)
    - RE 2 - Baseball - Softball (Box 187)
    - RE 3 - Bathing - Swimming (Box 187)
    - RE 6 - Boxing - Wrestling - Karate - Judo (Box 187)
    - RE 8 - Dancing (Box 187)
    - RE 10 - Football (Box 187)
    - RE 11 - Golf (Box 187)
    - RE 12 - Hockey (Box 187)
    - RE 13 - Hunting - Fishing (Box 187)
    - RE 14 - Olympic Games (Box 187)
    - RE 16 - Racing (Box 187)
    - RE 20 - Soccer (Box 187)
    - RE 21 - Tennis (Box 187)
    - RE 22 - Track & Field Meets (Box 187)
  - Religious Matters (RM), 48
    - RM - RELIGIOUS MATTERS (Box 187)
    - RM 1 - Bibles - Sunday Schools (Box 187)
    - RM 2 - Prayers - Prayer Periods (Box 187)
    - RM 3 - Religions (Box 187)
    - RM 3-1 - Catholic (Box 187)
    - RM 3-2 - Jewish (Box 187)
    - RM 3-3 - Protestant (Box 187)
    - RM 4 - Religious Services (Box 187)
  - Reports - Statistics (RS), 49
    - RS - REPORTS - STATISTICS (Box 188)
    - RS - REPORTS - STATISTICS, 1975 August (Box 188)
    - RS - REPORTS - STATISTICS, 1975 October (Box 188)
    - RS - REPORTS - STATISTICS, 1976 June (Box 188)
    - RS 1 - Annual - non-Government (by Organization)/A-Z (Box 188)
    - RS 2 - Population Censuses (Box 188)
    - RS 3 - Government Reports (Box 188)
    - RS 3 - Government Reports, 1976 January (Box 188)
    - RS 3-1 - Presidential Panel on Federal Compensation (Box 188)
    - RS 3-2 - Water Quality Commission Report (Box 188)
    - RS 3-2 - Water Quality Commission Report, 1976 March (Box 188)
    - RS 3-2 - Water Quality Commission Report, 1976 April 5 (Box 188)
    - RS 3-3 - Status Reports (Box 188)
    - RS 4 - Weekly Briefing Notes (Box 188)
  - Safety - Accident Prevention (SA), 50
    - SA - SAFETY - ACCIDENT PREVENTION (Box 188)
    - SA-1 - Fire (Box 188)
    - SA-2 - Highway - Traffic (Box 188)
    - SA-3 - Industrial Occupational (Box 188)
  - Sciences (SC), 51
    - SC - SCIENCES (Box 189)
    - SC - SCIENCES, 1975 July (Box 189)
    - SC 2 - Earth Sciences (Box 189)
    - SC 2-4 - Meteorology (Box 189)
    - SC 3 - Electronics (Box 189)
    - SC 4 - Engineering (Box 189)
    - SC 5 - Oceanography (Box 189)
    - SC 6 - Physical Sciences (Box 189)
  - Social Affairs (SO), 52
    - SO - SOCIAL AFFAIRS (Box 189)
    - SO 2 - Breakfasts (Box 189)
    - SO 3 - Dinners (VP Party for Staff), 1976 September 8 (Box 189)
    - SO 4 - Luncheons (Box 189)
    - SO 6 - Receptions (Box 189)
    - SO 7 - Teas - Garden Parties - Concerts - Housewarmings (Box 189)
    - SO 7 - Teas - Garden Parties - Concerts - Housewarmings, 1975 October (Box 189)
    - SO 7 - Teas - Garden Parties - Concerts - Housewarmings, 1975 November (Box 189)
  - States (ST), 53
    - ST 1 - Alabama (Box 192)
    - ST 2 - Alaska (Box 192)
    - ST 3 - Arizona (Box 192)
    - ST 4 - Arkansas (Box 192)
    - ST 5 - California (Box 192)
    - ST 6 - Canal Zone (Box 192)
    - ST 7 - Colorado (Box 192)
    - ST 8 - Connecticut (Box 192)
    - ST 9 - Delaware (Box 192)
    - ST 10 - District of Columbia (Box 192)
    - ST 11 - Florida (Box 192)
    - ST 12 - Georgia (Box 192)
    - ST 13 - Guam (Box 192)
    - ST 14 - Haiwaii (Box 192)
    - ST 15 - Idaho (Box 192)
    - ST 16 - Illinois (Box 192)
    - ST 17 - Indiana (Box 192)
    - ST 18 - Iowa (Box 192)
    - ST 19 - Kansas (Box 192)
    - ST 20 - Kentucky (Box 192)
    - ST 21 - Louisiana (Box 192)
    - ST 22 - Maine (Box 192)
    - ST 23 - Maryland (Box 192)
    - ST 24 - Massachusetts (Box 192)
    - ST 25 - Michigan (Box 192)
    - ST 26 - Minnesota (Box 192)
    - ST 27 - Mississippi (Box 192)
    - ST 28 - Missouri (Box 192)
    - ST 29 - Montana (Box 192)
    - ST 30 - Nebraska (Box 192)
    - ST 31 - Nevada (Box 192)
    - ST 32 - New Hampshire (Box 192)
    - ST 33 - New Jersey (Box 192)
    - ST 34 - New Mexico (Box 192)
    - ST 35 - New York (Box 192)
    - ST 36 - North Carolina (Box 192)
    - ST 37 - North Dakota (Box 192)
    - ST 38 - Ohio (Box 192)
    - ST 39 - Oaklahoma (Box 192)
    - ST 40 - Oregon (Box 192)
    - ST 41 - Pacific Island (Box 192)
    - ST 42 - Pennsylvania (Box 192)
    - ST 43 - Puerto Rico (Box 192)
    - ST 44 - Rhode Island (Box 192)
    - ST 45 - South Carolina (Box 192)
    - ST 46 - South Dakota (Box 192)
    - ST 47 - Tennessee (Box 192)
    - ST 48 - Texas (Box 192)
    - ST 49 - Utah (Box 192)
    - ST 50 - Vermont (Box 192)
    - ST 51 -Virginia (Box 192)
    - ST 52 - Virgin Islands (Box 192)
    - ST 53 - Washington (Box 192)
    - ST 54 - Wisconsin (Box 192)
    - ST 55 - West Virginia (Box 192)
    - ST 56 - Wyoming (Box 192)
    - ST 100 - State Conference (Box 192)
  - Trade (TA), 54
    - TA - TRADE (Box 192)
    - TA 1 - Boycotts (Box 192)
    - TA-1 - Boycotts/A-Z (Box 192)
    - TA 2 - Buy American (Box 192)
    - TA 3 - Exports (Box 192)
    - TA 4 - Tariff-Imports (Box 192)
    - TA 6 - Trade Centers (Box 192)
  - Transportation (TN), 55
    - TN - TRANSPORTATION (Box 192)
    - TN 1 - Highways (Box 192)
    - TN 2 - Commuter Transportation (Box 192)
    - TN 4 - Railroads (Box 192)
    - TN 7 - Water Transportation (Box 192)
  - Utilities (UT), 56
    - UT - UTILITIES (Box 198)
    - UT 1 - Communications - Telecommunications (Box 198)
    - UT 1-1 - Radio - Television (Box 198)
    - UT 1-3 - Telephone (Box 198)
    - UT 2 - Electricity (Box 198)
    - UT 2-1 - Public Power (Box 198)
    - UT 4 - Water Supply - City water system (Box 198)
  - Veterans Affairs (VA), 57
    - VA - VETERANS AFFAIRS (Box 198)
    - VA - VETERANS AFFAIRS/A-Z (by individual veteran) (Box 198)
    - VA 2 - Compensation - Pension (Box 198)
    - VA 3 - Educational Program (Box 198)
    - VA 4 - Hospitalization - Rehabilitation (Box 198)
  - Vice President (Personal) (VP), 58
    - VP - VICE PRESIDENT (PERSONAL) (Box 198)
    - VP 1 - Articles, books - written by Vice President (Box 198)
    - VP 2 - Articles, books - written about Vice President (Box 198)
    - VP 3 - Contributions made by Vice President (in his name) (Box 198)
    - VP 5 - Family (Box 198)
    - VP 5-1 - Mrs. Rockefeller (Box 198)
    - VP 6 - Income Tax (Box 198)
    - VP 7 - Lawsuits (Box 198)
    - VP 9 - Memberships (Box 198)
    - VP 9-1 - Memberships accepted (Box 198)
    - VP 9-1 - Memberships accepted (by organization)/A-Z (Box 198)
    - VP 9-2 - Memberships denied (by organization)/A-Z (Box 198)
    - VP 10 - Messages received (Box 198)
    - VP 10-1 - Birthday (Box 198)
    - VP 10-2 - Condolences - Sympathy (Box 198)
    - VP 10-2 - Condolences - Sympathy, 1976 June 8 (Box 198)
    - VP 10-2 - Condolences - Sympathy, 1976 June 9 (Box 198)
    - VP 10-2-1 - Illness (Box 198)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation (Box 198)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 January 10 (Box 198)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 January 15 (Box 198)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 January 21 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 January 24 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 January 28 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 February 1 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 February 6 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 February 11 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-3 - Election - Nomination - Confirmation, 1975 March 1 (Box 199)
    - VP 10-4 - Messages for Holidays (Box 199)
    - VP 10-5 - Inaugural-Anniversary (Box 199)
    - VP 10-6 - Wedding Anniversary (Box 199)
    - VP 10-7 - Appreciation for things done by the Vice President or his family (Box 200)
    - VP 10-7 - Appreciation for things done by the Vice President or his family, 1976 September (Box 200)
    - VP 10-7 - Appreciation for things done by the Vice President or his family, 1976 November (Box 200)
    - VP 10-7 - Appreciation for things done by the Vice President or his family, 1976 December (Box 200)
    - VP 11 - Names in honor of the Vice President (Box 200)
    - VP 13 - Personal Date on Vice President (Box 200)
    - VP 13-1 - Degrees tendered - conferred (Box 200)
    - VP 13-2 - Education (Box 200)
    - VP 13-3 - Genealogical Data (Box 200)
    - VP 13-4 - Health (Box 200)
    - VP 13-5 - Homes (Box 200)
    - VP 13-5-1 - Birthplace - Boyhood Home (Box 200)
    - VP 13-6 - Medals - Citations - Decorations (Box 200)
    - VP 13-7 - Military Service (Box 200)
    - VP 13-8 - Religious Affiliations (Box 200)
    - VP 15 - Preferences - Hobbies of Vice President (Box 200)
    - VP 15-1 - Arts - Artists - Paintings (Box 200)
    - VP 15-2 - Bible Passages - Prayers (Box 200)
    - VP 15-6 - Sports (Box 200)
    - VP 18 - Security or Protection of Vice President (Box 200)
    - VP 19 - Vice President Conduct in Public (Box 200)
  - Vice President's Office (VS), 59
    - VS - VICE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE (Box 201)
    - VS - VICE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE, 1975 June 13 (Box 201)
    - VS - VICE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE, 1975 July (Box 201)
    - VS - VICE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE, 1976 January (Box 201)
    - VS - VICE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE, 1976 February (Box 201)
    - VS - VICE PRESIDENT'S OFFICE, 1976 June (Box 201)
    - VS 1 - Budget (Box 201)
    - VS 3 - Ofice Management (correspondence) (Box 201)
    - VS 3-1 - Mail (Box 201)
    - VS 3-2 - Records - Files (Box 201)
    - VS 4-1-1 - Office Furnishings (Box 201)
    - VS 5 - Staff (Box 201)
    - VS 5 - Staff, 1975 June (Box 201)
    - VS 5-1 - Staff Meetings (Box 201)
    - VS 6 - Supplies - Material - Services (Box 201)
    - VS 7-2 - Telephone (Box 201)
    - VS 8 - Travel and Transportation for Staff (Box 201)
    - VS 9 - Vehicles (Box 201)
    - VS 9-1 - Airplanes - Helicopter (Box 201)
    - VS 9-2 - Automobiles (Box 201)
  - Welfare (WE), 60
    - WE - WELFARE (Box 201)
    - WE 1 - Children (Box 201)
    - WE 1-1 - Child Welfare Services (Box 201)
    - WE 1-2 - Crippled Children Services (Box 201)
    - WE 2-5 (Box 201)
    - WE 3 - Family Planning (Box 201)
    - WE 4 - Fund Drives (Box 201)
    - WE 4-1 - American Cancer Society (Box 201)
    - WE 4-4 - March of Dimes (Box 201)
    - WE 4-5 - Muscular Distrophy Association of America (Box 201)
    - WE 4-6 - National Society of Crippled Children (Box 201)
    - WE 4-9 - United Community Campaigns of America (Box 201)
    - WE 4-9-1 - Combined Federal Campaign (Box 201)
    - WE 5 - Geriatrics - Aged (Box 201)
    - WE 7 - Social Security (Box 201)
    - WE 8 - Vocational Rehabilitation (Box 201)
    - WE 9 - Youth Programs (Box 201)
    - WE 10-2 - Job Corps (Box 201)
- Chronological Files, 3
  Carbon copies of outgoing correspondence are filed in the name, subject, and chronological files. The chronological file contains only outgoing letters.
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1975 June 26-August 30 (Box 39)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1975 September 2-October 10 (Box 40)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1975 October 12-November 10 (Box 41)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1975 November 11-December 9 (Box 42)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1975 December 10 -1976 January 15 (Box 43)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 January 16-February 20 (Box 44)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 February 21-March 31 (Box 45)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 April 1-May 9 (Box 46)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 May 10-June 9 (Box 47)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 June 10-July 20 (Box 48)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 July 21-September 3 (Box 58)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 September 5-October 15 (Box 59)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 October 16-November 25 (Box 60)
  - CHRONOLOGICAL MATERIAL, 1976 November 26-1977 January 19 (Box 68)
- Invitations, 4
  Invitations to speak, appear, attend; most declined.
  Arrangement
  Invitations is arranged in 4 subseries: 1. General. 2. Domestic. 3. Foreign. 4. Other.
  Domestic invitations are primarily filed by the year of the event/state or geographic area in which the event is being held in/city the event is being held in.
  Each state or geographic area is assigned a number. The states are then arranged numerically/alphabetically. For example, ST 1 is Alabama, ST 2 is Alaska, ST 3 is Arizona and so on.
  If a folder becomes too large to hold invitations from a particular state or geographic area, it is then divided alphabetically by the name of the city. Cities represented by a significant amount of documentation will have their own folder, or multiple folders.
  Foreign invitations are primarily filed by the year of the event/country/city.
  - General, 4.1
    - Invitations (Box 19)
      Custodial History
      From Nancy Towell
    - Invitations (Box 20)
    - Invitations (Box 21)
    - Invitations (Box 22)
  - Domestic, 4.2
    - IV 1 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1974 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 1/ Alabama (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 2/Alaska (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 3/Arizona (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST4/Arkansas (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 5/California (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 5/California/Beverly Hills (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 5/California/Los Angeles (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 5/California/Sacramento (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 5/California/San Diego (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 5/California/San Francisco (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 6/Canal Zone (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 7/Colorado (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 8/Connecticut (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 9/Delaware (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 January 1-15 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 January 16-31 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 February 1-15 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 February 16-31 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 March 1-15 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 March 16-31 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/District of Columbia, 1975 April 1-15 (Box 49)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 April 16-30 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 May 1-15 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 May 16-30 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 June 1-15 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 June 16-30 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 July 1-15 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 July16-31 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 August 1-15 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 August 16-31 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 September 1-15 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 September 16-30 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 October 1-15 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 October 16-31 (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 November (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C., 1975 December (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 10/Washingto, D.C. (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 11/Florida (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 12/Georgia (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 13/Guam (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 14/Hawaii (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 15/Idaho (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 16/Illinois (Box 50)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 16/Illinois/Chicago (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 17/Indiana (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 18/Iowa (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 19/Kansas (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 20/Kentucky (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 21/Louisiana (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 22/Maine (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 23/Maryland (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 24Massachusetts (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 25/Michigan (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 26/Minnesota (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 27/Mississippi (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 28Missouri (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 29/Montana (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 30/Nebraska (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 31/Nevada (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 32/New Hampshire (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 33/New Jersey (Box 51)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 34/New Mexico (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Albany (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Brooklyn (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Bronx (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Buffalo (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Long Island (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 January (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 February (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 March (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 April (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 May (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 June (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 July (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 August (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 September (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 October (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 November (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/New York City, 1975 December (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Rochester (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New YorkSyracuse (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/White Plains (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Cities A-F (Box 52)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Cities G-J (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Cities K-L (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Cities M-P (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Cities Q-S (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 35/New York/Cities T-Z (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 36/North Carolina (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 37/North Dakota (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 38/Ohio (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 39/Oklahoma (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 40/Oregon (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 41/Pacific Island (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 42/Pennsylvania (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 43/Puerto Rico (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 44/Rhode Island (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 45/South Carolina (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 46/South Dakota (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 47/Tennessee (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 48/Texas (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 49/Utah (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 50/Vermont (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 51/Virginia/Arlington (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 51/Virginia/Norfolk (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 51/Virginia/Richmond (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 51/Virginia/Williamsburg (Box 53)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 51/Virginia/Cities A-L (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 51/Virginia/Cities M-Z (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 52/Virgin Islands (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 53/Washington (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 54/Wisconsin (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 55/West Virginia (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1975/ST 56/Wyoming (Box 54)
    - IV 1/1976 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 1 - Alabama (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 2 - Alaska (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 3 - Arizona (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 4 - Arkansas (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 5 - California (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 5 - California/Los Angeles (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 5 - California/San Francisco (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 6 - Canal Zone (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 7 - Colorado (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 8 - Connecticut (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 9 - Delaware (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 January 1 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 January 16 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 February 1 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 February 16 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 March 1 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 March 16 (Box 202)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 April 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 April 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 May 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 May 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 June 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 June 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 July 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 July 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 August 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 August 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 September 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 September 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 October 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 October 16 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 10 - District of Columbia, 1976 November 1 (Box 203)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 11 - Florida (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 11 - Florida/Miami and Miami Beach (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 12 - Georgia (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 13 - Guam (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 14 - Hawaii (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 15 - Idaho (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 16 - Illinois (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 16 - Illinois/Chicago (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 17 - Indiana (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 18 - Iowa (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 19 - Kansas (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 20 - Kentucky (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 21 - Louisiana (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 22 - Maine (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 23 - Maryland (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 24 - Massachusetts (Box 204)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 25 - Michigan (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 26 - Minnesota (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 27 - Mississippi (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 28 - Missouri (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 29 - Montana (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 30 - Nebraska (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 31 - Nevada (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 32 - New Hampshire (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 33 - New Jersey (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 34 - New Mexico (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York/Cities/A-B (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York/Cities/C-K (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York/Cities/L-O (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York/Cities/P-R (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York/Cities/S-Z (Box 205)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 January (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 February (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 March (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 April (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 May (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 June (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 July (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 August (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 September (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 October (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 November (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 35 - New York City, 1976 December (Box 206)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 36 - North Carolina (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 37 - North Dakota (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 38 - Ohio (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 39 - Oklahoma (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 40 - Oregon (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 41 - Pacific Island (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 42 - Pennsylvania (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 42 - Pennsylvania/Philadelphia (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 43 - Puerto Rico (Box 207)
    - IV 1/1976/ST 44 - Rhode Island (Box 207)